Guide to the Cayuga Trails Club records, 1957-2012.
Cayuga Trails Club records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cayuga Trails Club records, 1957-2012.
3833
Cayuga Trails Club.
3.4 cubic ft.
Ephemera, maps, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes newsletters entitled CAYUGA TRAILS; membership lists; Executive Board minutes; committee annual reports; correspondence; committee materials; materials concerning hikes; maps; guide book, including the 1964 draft and the fifth edition, GUIDE TO TRAILS OF THE FINGER LAKES REGION, 1983; and other miscellaneous items of the Cayuga Trails Club, Ithaca, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes newsletters entitled CAYUGA TRAILS; membership lists; Executive Board minutes; committee annual reports; correspondence; committee materials; materials concerning hikes; maps; guide book, including the 1964 draft and the fifth edition, GUIDE TO TRAILS OF THE FINGER LAKES REGION, 1983; and other miscellaneous items of the Cayuga Trails Club, Ithaca, New York.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cayuga Trails Club.; Cayuga Trails Club.
Titles:
Cayuga trails.
Subjects:
Hiking--New York (State)--Finger Lakes.; Trails--New York (State)--Finger Lakes.
Places:
Finger Lakes (N.Y.)--Description and travel.
Form and Genre Terms:
Maps.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hikers Register, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1961-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Activities - from records of Lawrence Grinnell, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Committee materials, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Meeting notes, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Suggested trips or meetings, 1962-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Standard Practices, By-Laws, 1962-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Legal correspondence, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Permissions, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Members, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Former members, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Finger Lakes Trail property owners, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Legal documents, 1965-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Elkins, Leonard, President, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Owners' list, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Trail reports, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Trail scouting reports, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Trail scouting and maintenance, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Seneca Trails permission, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Trail guide, maps, 1971, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Executive Board minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cayuga "Trail Register", 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cayuga Trails Club membership lists, 1975-1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Executive Board minutes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Executive Board minutes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Treasurer's reports, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Executive Board minutes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Executive Board minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Permissions - abandoned, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cayuga Trails Club patch, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Minutes, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Minutes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Secretary's records, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Executive Board minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Minutes, reports, other business, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Secretary's records, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Rieman Woods, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Rieman Woods, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Rieman Woods and Nature Conservancy, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Walk, Look and Learn (W.L.L.) Hikes, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- W.L.L., 1998-1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- W.L.L., 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- W.L.L., 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Certificates of Recognition, et al, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- W.L.L., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Cayuga Trails Club newsletters, 1961-2012 (Box 2)
- Notebook - "Publicity", 1961-1972 (Box 3)
- Finger Lakes Trail Conference Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Finger Lakes Trail Conference material, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Finger Lakes Trail Conference correspondence, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Finger Lakes Trail Conference Inc., "The Trailetter", 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Trail Manual for Finger Lakes Trail (FLT) - and Conversion Table - Measuring Wheel, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Land Owners - Finger Lakes Trails Numeric Order, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- FLT Permissions - Caroline Section, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- FLT Permissions - Connecticut Hill Section, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- FLT Permissions - Danby Section and Buttermilk Spur, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- FLT Permissions - Seneca Lake Section, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- FLT correspondence re permissions, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- FLT early measurements, trail description, maps, owner lists (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Finger Lakes Trail News, 1962-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13-21)
- Newsletter of the North Country Trail Association, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 22-24)
- Foothills Trail Club News, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Bruce Trail, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Adirondack Mountain Club, 1966-1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Membership List, 1978-1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Committee Reports, ca. 1970-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Guide, 4th Draft, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Trail Maps: Cayuga Trail, Sierra Club/TC3 Outings Club/Dryden Sections, Interloken Trail, Art Kopp Trail Section, Caroline Section, Seneca Lake Section, Connecticut Hill Section, Danby Section (Box 5)
- Guide to Trails of the Finger Lakes Region - 1964, 1967, 1971, 1983, 1993 (Box 5)
- Oversized hand drawn trail maps (Mapcase-folder 1)